AND BECAUSE THEY WERE
SUCH BIG MOANA FANS,
DISNEY INVITED THEM TO
A PARTY WITH THE
STARS. OH!
WHERE THEY GOT TO
MEET THEM.
HAVE YOU HAD IT
TODAY?
YEAH!
AND TAKE LOTS OF
PICTURES.
BUT I HAD ONE
MORE SURPRISE. AND I
WANTED TO TAKE THIS
WISH ONE STEP FURTHER
BY SURPRISING THEM AT
THE MOANA PREMIERE. THIS
IS THE KIDS IN
THIS LIMO. HAVE NO
IDEA I'M HERE.
HOW'S IT GOING?
OH MY GOD! HEY!
IT'S NICE TO MEET
YOU! GO ON HERE!
NICE TO MEET YOU!
YOU GUYS WANT TO
GO WATCH MOANA? YEAH!
ALRIGHT, LET'S GO GET
OUR SEATS! WHAT DO
YOU GUYS THINK SO
FAR? IT'S JUST LIKE
AN AWESOME.
YEAH?
SHOUT OUT TO DISNEY
FOR LETTING US WATCH
THE MOVIE EARLY. WHEN
YOU SEE THIS VIDEO,
THAT MEANS IT'S ABOUT
TO GO WATCH MOANA
RIGHT NOW.
THEN I HAD DISNEY.
THE LARGEST WISH -GRANNER
IN THE WORLD.
HELP ME WITH THIS
NEXT ONE. HOW'S IT
GOING?
YES?
OH MY GOD!
I HEARD YOU'RE A
BIG FAN. OH MY
GOD.
OH MY GOD. GOD.
HOW'S IT GOING?
TELL ME YOU'RE A
BIG FAN. WOW, YOU'RE
MAKING ME CRY. YEAH,
THEY TOLD ME YOU'RE
A BIG FAN OF
THE CHANNEL, SO I
WANT TO COME SAY
HI.
YOU WANT TO GIVE
IT ANOTHER HUG?
THAT'S NICE TO MEET
YOU, EMMANUEL.
WISHES LIKE THESE ARE
FULFILLED EVERY DAY BY
DISNEY,
WISH -GRANTING ORGANIZATIONS,
AND GIVE KIDS THE
WORLD A NONPROFIT THAT
GIVES CHILDREN WITH CRITICAL
ILLNESSES AND THEIR FAMILY
A WEEK LONG, COST
-FREE VACATION TO CREATE
SOME OF THEIR MOST
PRICELESS MEMORIES TOGETHER.
AND YOU CAN GET
BACK TO THEM BY
DONATING FOR A CHANCE
TO WIN A NIGHT
AT THE MOST EXCLUSIVE
ROOM IN THE ENTIRE
WORLD.
CINDERELLA'S CASTLE SWEET.
WE ARE IN THE
MIDDLE OF DISNEY WORLD
ON TOP OF THE
CASTLE. THIS IS A
ONE -OF -ONE ROOM
THAT YOU CAN'T BUY
ANYWHERE. AND YOU AT
HOME COULD LITERALLY STAY
IN THIS ROOM. ALL
YOU HAVE TO DO
IS DONATE $10 TO
GIVE KIDS THE WORLD,
WHICH DOES EXACTLY WHAT
YOU SAW IN THIS
VIDEO. IT GIVES KIDS
WHO ARE AT THE
LOWEST POINT OF THEIR
LIFE, SOMETHING TO LOOK
FORWARD TO, IT GIVES
THEM JOY AND WE
SHOULD SUPPORT THEM. SO
CLICK THE LINK IN
THE DESCRIPTION FOR YOUR
CHANCE TO WIN.
AND AFTER TRAVELING ALL
AROUND THE WORLD,
OUR BIGGEST WISHERS WANTED
TO BE ANONYMOUS, AND
HE ASKED THAT WE
HOPE OTHER CANCER PATIENTS,
WHICH IS EXACTLY WHAT
WE'RE DOING WITH A
MASSIVE BLOOD DRIVE.
CAN YOU EXPLAIN WHAT
WE'RE DOING RIGHT NOW?
WE ARE GIVING BLOOD,
RED BLOOD CELLS AND
WHITE BLOOD CELLS TO
HELP PATIENTS WHO NEED
IT. OBVIOUSLY, EVERYONE HERE
IS GIVING BLOOD TO
SAVE LIVES, BUT THEY'RE
PROBABLY WONDERING, HOW DOES
THIS SAVE LIVES? WHEN
THEY GIVE YOU